systweak.com 2019-12-27

# Systweak Software – Privacy Policy

  1. #####  Legalities of using personal data. 

The General Data Protection Regulation (EU) 2016/679 ("GDPR"), effective May 25, 2018. GDPR mandates that personal data should only be process under a legal binding. The legal binding may differ depending on the country or jurisdiction. Details for legalities that we follow when using your data are listed below. 

In Simple Words: We use these legalities for processing data subject to the GDPR. 

  2. #####  Contract of performance 

Your personal data will be used in accordance to the agreement we have. To explain let’s take an example: to purchased, register and maintain your account we will make sure that the product functions in a secure way and responds to your requests.

  3. #####  Sincere interests 

Your personal data may be used for our sincere interests. For example, we trust our legal interests to analyze and improve our products, content on the website, to send you information about product update or information related to products or use of your information for legal purpose, administrative and fraud detection. 

  4. #####  Legal implications 

Your personal data may be used to follow legal requirements, as explained in omission 4, above. 

  5. #####  Consent 

At certain occasions we may seek your consent to perform certain action using your personal data. When doing so we will be transparent about sharing your details so that you are aware of what you are agreeing to. 

  6. #####  Choice 

We have partnership with third parties to manage and display our advertisement on other sites. For this they may use cookies or likewise technologies to show advertisement based on your browsing activities and interests. However, if you wish to opt out of interest-based advertising [click here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/) [or if located in the European Union [click here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/) ]. Please note you will continue to receive generic ads. 

To receive email, newsletter, or other communications from us you can sign up. But once you communicate with us by downloading a product or by visiting our website you may be added to the mailing list. However, if you want to stop receiving any information from us you can use the “Unsubscribe” link sent in the mails or you can contact us at [privacypolicy@systweak.com](mailto:privacypolicy@systweak.com "Email Address"). 

  7. #####  Report Detected Infections 

You may opt out of sample collection in certain Systweak products by using the steps mentioned below. These samples are collected to analysis malware infected files detected on your machine. 

In Simple Words: We give you all the control to manage your data. 

  8. #####  Using Advanced System Protector for Home on Windows: 

Launch Advanced System Protector 

Here, click on Quarantine tab > Logs. 

At the bottom of the screen uncheck “Yes, I want to improve Advanced System Protector, by allowing it to report detected infections to servers.” 

Once you do so, no longer the infectious file will be sent to our servers. 

  9. #####  Security 

We take all necessary security measures to protect your personal data from unauthorized access, use and leak. However, there is no fully secure method to store or send data over Internet, therefore, we cannot guarantee complete security of your personal data. 

In Simple Words: We do all that is necessary to secure your data. 

  10. #####  Retaining 

We may keep your personal data as needed to carry out the purpose for which it was collected. Your personal data may be used to fulfill our business needs, legal duties, protection of assets, and implement our agreements. These needs may vary depending on the product or service. 

In Simple Words: We keep your personal data only to support our product and for the reason it is collected. 

  11. #####  Links 

Our website may encompass link to some third-party websites, if you give any information on these links then the owner of that site will be directly responsible for your privacy. Before sharing any information, you should read terms and conditions of that site as we will not handle the content, privacy, or security of that site and services. 

In Simple Words: Our privacy policy is applied only till the time you are on our site, if you visit a third-party site we will not be responsible. 

  12. #####  Updating or Removal of your personal data 

To know what all data we may have about you, contact us by sending email to [privacypolicy@systweak.com](mailto:privacypolicy@systweak.com "Email Address"). Besides, if you want to delete the information you can contact us at [privacypolicy@systweak.com](mailto:privacypolicy@systweak.com "Email Address") we will respond to you in a realistic timeframe and will delete your personal data. However, some information may be kept in backup copies for our record or as needed by the law. We may keep your information for as long as you use the services or your account is active, to deal with legal responsibilities and to resolve arguments and apply our agreements. 

In Simple Words: Subjected to law we will delete or alter your information if asked. 

  13. #####  International 

Your personal data may be transferred to, and maintained on, computers located outside of your state, province, country, or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide your personal data to us, we may transfer your personal data to the United States and process it there. 

Systweak participates in and has certified its compliance with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework. Systweak is committed to subjecting all personal data received from European Union (EU) member countries, in reliance on the Privacy Shield Framework, to the Framework's applicable Principles. To learn more about the Privacy Shield Framework, visit the U.S. Department of Commerce's [ Privacy Shield List. ](https://www.privacyshield.gov/list)

Systweak is responsible for the processing of personal data it receives, under the Privacy Shield Framework, and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. Systweak complies with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers of personal data from the EU, including the onward transfer liability provisions. 

With respect to personal data received or transferred pursuant to the Privacy Shield Framework, Systweak is subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. In certain situations, Systweak may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. 

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third-party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at <https://www.jamsadr.com/eu-us-privacy-shield>. 

Under certain conditions, more fully described on the Privacy Shield website, you may invoke binding arbitration when other dispute resolution procedures have been exhausted. 

In Simple Words: If you're not in the U.S., we may transfer your information to the U.S. We participate in the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework. 

  14. #####  Children 

We do not collect any personal data knowingly about children under thirteen. Our services are not designed for children under eighteen. However, we learn that any personal data of an adolescent is collected we will delete all such information from our files ASAP. But this information may still be in our record as backup copies or as otherwise required by the law. 

In Simple Words: We do not collect children information intentionally, and if collected accidently we do delete it.
